本字幕由YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
■
翻译：红豆包    IZ    奈奈良    糯
校对：糯      时间轴：今
■
后期：森    总监：萌
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第四集
好了孩子们  都知道怎么做吧
Okay, kids, you know the plan.
船一靠岸
When the ship docks,
吉恩  "嘭"  你就喊话
Gene, bam, bullhorn!
全员弃船
Abandon ship!
来吃汉堡吧
For Bob's Burgers.
然后  蒂娜  大家一上岸
Then, Tina, when people start coming ashore,
"嘭"  你就发券
pow, coupons!
所有乘客都享受半价优惠  嘭
50% off to all cruise ship passengers. Pow.
说"噗"  这样更吸引人
Try "poo". That always gets attention.
-对啊对啊  -不行
- Oh, yeah, yeah. - No.
-噗  -用扩音器说
- Poo. - Use the bullhorn.
-不行  -噗
- No. - Poo.
随便吧  只是别再说别的了
Never mind. Just don't say anything.
没错  别再说别的了
Yeah, don't say anything.
人呢
Where is everybody?
优惠券都发完了吗
Did you hand out the coupons?
发完了  等一下
Yes. Oh, wait.
不  怎么回事  明明已经演练过了
No! What happened? We practiced!
我们觉得烦了  老爸
We choked, dad!
我们本来是想发优惠券来着
We planned on handing them out,
可是一转眼就到了中午
but then it was noon,
然后有一只虫子落在了地上
and then there was a bug that landed on the ground,
总之  时间就这么过去了
and anyway, the day just got away from us.
我的天
Oh, God...
嘟嘟嘟  有人穿了一套白色衣服
Rooty-toot-toot, someone's wearing a white suit!
我觉得那是船长  琳
I think that's the captain, Lin.
白色裤子  碰碰运气
White pants, take a chance.
可以上船吗
Permission to come aboard?
当然可以啦
Permission given!
我是弗拉缇船长
I'm Captain Flarty.
这里欢迎水手用餐吗
Is this restaurant seaman friendly?
从缅因州到墨西哥的汉堡我都吃过
You know, I've tried burgers from Maine to Mexico,
属你们家汉堡最好吃  鲍勃
but this is the best burger I've ever had, Bob.
谢谢
Um, thank you.
你可以向乘客推荐一下我们的汉堡
Maybe you could encourage your passengers to try our burgers.
我帮你们一个更大的忙
I'll do you one better.
来我的船上当客座厨师
Join me as a guest chef
我们这次要去波多黎各
on our cruise to Puerto Rico.
真的吗
Really?
当然  你的家人可以同去
Your family will accompany you, of course.
十天航程  费用我掏
Ten days, all expenses paid.
这邀请  确实大方
Wow, that's, that's quite an offer...
可是我们真的承担不起
Uh... but we really can't afford
闭店这么长时间
to leave this place for that long.
真是的
Come on!
而且  我还要等送肉的
Also, I'm-I'm supposed to get a meat delivery,
和送泡菜的  还有...
and the pickle guy's coming, too, and...
你是在拒绝我吗
You're turning me down?
是的  对不起
Yeah. Sorry?
那么  你能不能至少帮我个忙
Well, then, would you at least do me the honor
在今晚出发之前
of cooking just for tonight, Bob,
去船上为我们做顿大餐如何
at the captain's table while we're docked?
答应他  答应他  答应他
Say yes, say yes, say yes!
好吧
Um... Sure.
-太好了  -太好了
- Uh, yes. - Yeah!
-还算可以  -我们接受了
- Well, it's something. - We'll take it.
好极了
Outstanding!
同时  你的家人  当然也会
And meanwhile, your family will have, of course,
全程免费  我可是  说话算话
free run of the ship, and I, I do mean free.
给你贵宾卡  鲍勃的女人
Take this VIP card, bride of Bob.
妇孺优先
Women and children first.
还有贵宾
And VIPs!
告诉你们  这艘船...
Everyone, listen! This ship is...
非常豪华  他是想说"豪华"吗
Fancy? Was he gonna say fancy?
-很性感  -怀孕了
- Sexy? - Pregnant?
是个老太太
A grand old dame?
别说出来  给我们留个惊喜吧
Don't tell us! Let it be a surprise!
什么事这么好笑
What's so funny?
我就是...看到了一条好笑的鱼
Oh, just, uh... funny fish I saw.
如果你说的是那条  它非常欢实
If it's that one, it's hilarious.
如果你说的是那条  它已经死了
If it's that one, it's dead,
一点也不好笑
which isn't funny.
欢迎乘坐防风号游轮  贝尔彻一家
Welcome aboard the Windbreaker, Belchers!
谢谢你  船长
Uh, thank you, Captain.
这是我们第一次...
This is our first time on...
琪琪喜欢你  接着说
Kiki likes you! Go on.
别害怕
Oh, don't be afraid,
拍拍他  拍拍他 不了  谢谢
pet him, pet him. Uh, no, thanks.
这  这
What is, what is...
我希望你拍拍他 这是什么东西
I want you to pet him. what is he?
水豚  你是不是水豚啊
He's a capybara. Aren't you a capybara?
这是体型最大的啮齿类动物
It's the largest member of the rodent family...
仅次于吉恩
After Gene.
苍天啊
Oh, God.
琪琪  你拉了好多哦  真棒
Oh, Kiki! That's a big BM, yes.
好了  晚餐六点开始
All right, dinner's at six bells.
我的大副  阿希先生  会带你去厨房
My first mate here, Mr. Asch, will show you to the galley.
然后你给我们展示一下汉堡的做法
And you'll show the captain's table how burgers are done.
-好了鲍鲍  祝你做得愉快  -好吧
- All right, Bobby, have fun cooking! - Yeah.
走吧  孩子们
Come on, kids.
我很想看看
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
琪琪和老爸的腿能缠绵到什么地步
I want to see how far Kiki gets with dad's leg.
是的
Yeah!
鲍勃  这位是主厨  杜瓦尔
Bob, this is our head chef, Duval.
我还有事  失陪了
If you'll excuse me, duty calls.
我的替补厨师
My replacement.
我希望你能罩上脸和胳膊
I hope that you have a hairnet for your face and arms.
我不是来顶替你的
I'm not replacing you.
我只在今晚做一顿饭
I'm just cooking one meal for one night
为了这个船长
for the captain's table.
你让我想起了从前
You remind me of me,
当时我也接受了船长的特别邀请
back when I was the captain's special guest chef
为他做了一顿晚餐
for just "one night"
一做做了56次航程
56 voyages ago!
面包卷好了
Ah, there's the dinner rolls.
你的计时器怎么这个动静
Why does your timer sound like that?
这可是法国货
It's French!
好了  那边有个电影院
Okay, over there is the movie theater,
再往前是一面攀岩墙
and beyond that is the rock-climbing wall.
会说话的海牛
赫尔曼与玛丽莲
精彩现场  每晚呈现
会说话的海牛
A talking manatee?!
我不知道这是什么  可是我要看看
I don't know what that is, but I got to see it!
好吧  那我们女生去做做水疗吧
All right. Us girls are gonna go hit the spa.
我不去了
Pass.
我要去给在遮阳棚底下
I'm gonna go write dirty words
晒太阳的那些人后背上写些脏话
on sunbathers' backs in sunscreen.
好耶
Yeah.
我可不想把时间浪费在...
I'd rather not spend all day in a...
我要去做水疗
I can go to the spa.
你看你  用昂贵的牛肉做汉堡
Look at you, making hamburgers with your fancy beef
给高贵的船长当晚餐  黏黏糊糊先生
for the fancy captain's table, Mr. Squishy-Squashy.
普通乘客将会品尝这锅新鲜美味的蔬菜汤
The regular passengers will be enjoying my fresh vegetable stew.
那锅里的菜就没有新鲜的
Um, none of those vegetables are fresh.
乘客不会介意的
The passengers don't care.
他们喝不到的时候才会抱怨
They only complain if we run out.
如果他们抱怨  船长就会生气
And when they complain, the captain gets angry.
他有点不正常吧
Is he a little crazy?
小点声  他能听到的
Shh! He can hear you.
他在干酪刨丝器里装了一个微型麦克
He put a microphone in the cheese grater.
表现得自然点
Act normal.
来啊  哼  哼
Come on. Hum, hum.
好吧
Okay. Uh...
就是这样  自然地哼一哼
That's it. Humming like normal.
很好
Okay.
他曾是《寻星》地区大赛的决赛选手
He's a former regional Star Search finalist.
她是这片海洋最性感的海牛
She's the sexiest sea cow on the ocean.
他们是赫尔曼和玛丽莲
Together they're Herman and Marilyn!
你昨晚为什么在外面待到那么晚  玛丽莲
Why were you out so late last night, Marilyn?
听我解释  来上我嘛
Listen to this one. Always up my butt.
性感小姐  海洋小姐
Ooh-ooh-ooh, sexy lady, ocean lady.
这比晒太阳安全多了
This is so much safer than the sun.
来  烤烤我
Come on, cook me.
我不能接待未成年人  这是规定
I can't work on minors. Ship's regulations.
我会被炒掉的
I could lose my job.
马克  如果我说我的臀部肌肉
Marco, what if I told you I'm holding
紧张到生命受到威胁 你会怎样
a life-threatening amount of tension in my glutes?
臀部不行
No glutes.
-小腿呢  -不行
- Calves? - No.
-腰部呢  -不行
- Haunches? - No.
小肚子呢  -不行
Muffin top? - No.
大肉背呢 -不行  只能给你按摩头部
Back fat? -No. Top of head only.
好
Deal.
别停下
Don't stop.
弗朗西斯卡  我不想待这儿
Francesca, I don't want to be here,
你也不想待这儿
you don't want to be here.
不如咱们各得其乐
So let's make the best of it.
这个你能做吗
Can you do this?
帮我取消其他预约
Ooh! Cancel the rest of my appointments.
做好了
Nailed it!
不如有空跳到海里来看看我
Why don't you jump into the ocean and see me sometime?
你叫什么啊  小帅哥
What's your name, handsome?
我不叫小帅哥  我叫吉恩
No, it's Gene.
你好吉恩  你很卫生
Hi, Gene. Hygiene.
这个梗可以多用用嘛
Something this one could use a little more of.
好吧  至少我的笑话是新的
Well, at least my jokes are fresh.
笑话  什么笑话
Jokes? What jokes?
你只是个捧哏的
You're the straight man.
我讲笑话灵活着呢
I use the term loosely.
你很灵活[淫荡]嘛
Well, you know loose.
我更喜欢称之为"富有弹性"
I prefer to be called "flexible".
我裤子好像湿了  先闪了
My pants feel funny! Good-bye!
我需要一杯夏日沁饮来搭配我的夏日造型
I need a summer drink to go with my new summer glow!
艾萨克  来杯代基里酒
Hey, Isaac, Daiquiri me!
谁想来点开胃点心
Who wants apps?
我全要了
I'll take them all!
吉恩  头顶按摩好舒服哦
Hi, Gene. My scalp massage was fantastic.
谢谢关心
Thanks for asking.
-腹语表演好看吗  -很诡异
- How was the puppet show? - Weird.
我一直想尿尿  但是我忍住了
I felt like I had to pee the whole time, but I didn't.
给这杯代基里酒配件破烂婚纱吧
Whoo, throw a ripped wedding dress on this Daiquiri
指酒杯装饰物
因为它不是处女
cause it is not a virgin!
拿去给自己多刷点小费
Go ahead and give yourself a big tip on goldie.
这是我儿子
And this is my son.
你肯定看不出来  因为他很白我很黑
You can't tell cause he's pale and I'm so dark,
帮我看着他  好吗
but take care of him, all right?
那个钟情于你的小子
Looks like the boy who's sweet on you
看来是个富二代呢
has a silver spoon sticking out of his mouth.
这下饭钱不用愁了
I think we just found our meal ticket.
杜瓦尔  你的汗流到锅里了
Duval, you're sweating into your stew.
省得放盐了
Eh, saves on salt.
我去
Oh, God.
还好做完这一顿就可以走人了
I'm glad I'm leaving after this meal.
这里热死了
It's like a hundred degrees in here.
不好意思  风扇在我这里
Oh, sorry. I was hogging the fan.
好了  根本没用  谢了
Okay. That doesn't work. Thanks.
-给你凉快凉快  -谢谢
- Cool off. - Thank you.
-凉快凉快  -给我拿走
- Cool off. - Take it away.
来嘛来嘛
Here you are.
你杵我脸上了
It's on my face.
拜托  这位女士  让她继续
Come on, lady. Let her play it.
你已经喝掉很多了
You've had plenty.
是牡蛎吗
Oysters?
这是明天的早午餐
Yes, they're for the brunch tomorrow.
杜瓦尔  这些牡蛎都变质了
Duval, these oysters are spoiled.
-你才被宠坏了呢  -好吧
- You're spoiled. - Okay.
我不知道为何会有这种想法
I don't know why I thought
你好像很喜欢用这个做菜
you'd be interested in that,
但是  千万别用
but, uh, don't serve those.
-我要用  -千万别
- I am serving them. - Don't serve those.
我就要用
I'm serving them.
船长想向厨师道谢
Captain would like to thank the chef.
-是吗  -我是指鲍勃
- Oh! - I meant Bob.
悄悄话  很重要
Psst. Urgent whisper.
稍后  308房见
Meet me later. Cabin 308.
我吗
Me?
不  我在跟年轻的大帅哥说话
No, the other handsome young man I'm whispering to.
我很想去  但我们吃完甜点就要走了
I wish I could, but we're leaving after dessert.
如果你想尝些甜头...
Well, if you're looking for something sweet...
你在跟谁说悄悄话  他吗
Who are you whispering to! Him?
别招惹他
Oh, leave him alone.
你才别招惹他
You leave him alone.
我看你今晚已经够丢人的了
I think you've embarrassed yourself enough for one night!
别忘了  308房
Remember, Cabin 308!
各位贵宾  请用防风号最热烈的掌声
Honored guests, let's give a big Windbreaker salute
欢迎鲍勃・贝尔彻
to guest chef Bob Belcher!
那是我的男人
That's my man!
给你们做出汉堡  跟我做出孩子
He made your burgers and he made my babies!
好了孩子们  来  我们该...
Okay, kids, come on, time to go...
这船在动吗
Are we moving?
鲍勃・贝尔彻  掌声欢迎
Bob Belcher, everyone.
陆地呢
Where's the land?
陆地呢  陆地呢
Where's the land? Where's the land!
-就在下站  波多黎各  -啥
- Next stop, Puerto Rico. - What?!
看来你最终还是要做我的私人厨师
Looks like you'll be my private chef after all.
不  你不能...
No, you can't do...
琳达  我们被拐了
Linda, we're being shanghaied!
要去上海了
Shanghaied?
要去古中国旅行喽
Ooh! Ancient Chinese vacation!
-好耶  -太棒了
- Yay! - Yahoo!
大胸妹
Boobies!
-啥  -没什么
- What? - Nothing.
好了  木已成舟了鲍勃
All right, steady as she goes, Bob.
我可不会把一个全程付费的十天航程
I wouldn't call a ten-day, all expense paid cruise
说成是"被拐了"
"being shanghaied".
可是你不能强迫我的家人
But you can't force my family
也在这破船上待十天啊
to be on this crazy boat for ten days.
好了啦  鲍鲍  我们是在度假
Oh, come on, Bobby. It's a vacation.
这是你应得的  我们也一样
You deserve it. We all do.
别再抗拒了
Stop fighting it.
这是哪门子度假  琳达  这是绑架
This isn't a vacation, Linda, it's a kidnapping.
这就是一条黑船
This is a slave ship.
你迷糊了  鲍勃
You're disoriented, Bob.
有的人坐船就会变成这样
It happens to some people when they're at sea.
只要放松放松  就适应了
You'll adjust once you let yourself relax.
是啊  鲍勃  别闹了
Yeah, Bob. Give in.
家里又没丢什么
We're not missing anything at home.
鲍勃  我是德米翠
Hey, Bob, it's Demetri.
我把你订的肉放外面了啊
I'm gonna leave your meat outside.
你和琳达都在楼上吧
Uh, you and Linda are probably upstairs.
"五分钟就完事"  对吧老兄
"Back in five minutes," right, buddy?
好了
All right.
我们去甲板上商量吧  鲍勃
Let's discuss your concerns on the bridge, Bob,
那里有船靠岸无线电  可以免费使用
where there's s a ship-to-shore radio you're free to use.
你可以向人呼救并做好安排
You can call someone and make arrangements.
-好吧  -走吧  爷们
- All right. - All right, good man.
我让他来开船
I'm gonna let him steer the boat.
这法子最奏效
That always works.
好好度假吧
You'll get your vacation.
孩子们  看来我们可以好好享受
Kids, looks like we're on this Puerto Rican cruise
波多黎各之旅啦
for the whole enchilada.
这下可以去308房了
So, now I can go to Room 308.
308房里有什么
What's in Room 308?
我也不知道
I don't know!
不知道马克九点时有没有头部按摩预约
I wonder if Marco has a 9:00 scalp shiatsu.
我来给你按摩头皮  蒂娜
I'll massage your scalp, Tina.
然后会怎么样
So, how does this work?
海岸警卫队会派船过来还是...
The coast guard sends a boat for us or...
等等  这里不是甲板
Wait, this isn't the bridge.
这里是厨房
This is the galley.
还是你未来十天的家
And your home for the next ten days.
你真是疯了
You're out of your mind.
没错  是饿疯了
Yes... with hunger.
快去做饭  我还能吃下一个汉堡呢
Now get cooking, cause I've got room for another burger.
看来琪琪又拉了呢
And oh! Oh, it looks like Kiki does, too.
-让他拉完  -是  长官
- Let him finish! - Yes, sir.
跑吧  鲍勃
Go ahead, Bob.
继续跑吧  跑吧
Go ahead, run!
除非你会水上漂  否则你无处可逃
Unless you can run on water, there's nowhere for you to go!
妈的  你说得对
Damn it, you're right!
现在是谁疯了  鲍勃
Who's crazy now, Bob?
依然是你
You still are!
鲍勃
Bob.
全体船员注意  我是船长
Attention crew, this is your captain.
我们的大胡子特邀厨师行踪不明
Our mustachioed guest chef has gone missing.
第一个找到他的人将会取回护照
First one to find him gets their passport back.
好了  我来试试这些宝贝
All right, let's see what these babies can do.
不不不不不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
弗朗西斯卡
Francesca!
马克  我长大了四个小时
Hey, Marco. I'm four hours older.
现在可以给我按摩脖子了吗
Maybe you can rub my neck now?
别累着他
Don't tire him out.
你们有老虎机吗
Do you have penny slots?
有啊
Yes, we do.
给我一卷硬币  我预感手气不错
Give me a whole roll of pennies cause I feel lucky.
谁呀
Who is it?
吉恩
It's Gene.
我不能说太久  他在洗澡
I can't talk long, he's in the shower.
这个杯子送给你
I got you this mug.
希望你能"铭记"这次航行
I hope you "heart" cruising.
谢谢你
Thank you.
玛丽莲  你在跟谁讲话
Marilyn, who are you talking to?
客房服务
Uh, room service!
他很善妒
He's jealous.
他从不让我离开他的视线
He never lets me out of his sight.
我只需要100块钱就能换个新的造型
I just need 100 bucks for new headshots,
然后就能单飞了
then I can go solo.
我上哪去弄100块钱啊
But where, oh, where will I get 100 dollars?!
或许你...
Well, maybe you...
吉恩  谢谢你
Oh, Gene, thank you!
我会还给你的  我发誓
It'll just be a loan, I promise.
先付给你头期利息
Here's your first interest payment.
玛丽莲  你总是不擦座位
Marilyn, you never wipe the seat!
到处都是海水
There's sea water everywhere!
快跑  我的小心肝
Run, my little cabbage!
冲向100块
Run to 100 dollars!
好的
Yes!
救命  救命  我们被绑架了
Help! SOS! We've been kidnapped!
抱歉  再说一遍
Sorry, please repeat!
我们被绑架了  我们全家都在这艘船上
We've been kidnapped! My family's on this boat!
一切都正常还是遇到麻烦了
Is everything okay or is there a problem?
船长是个疯子
The-The captain is crazy!
救救我们
Help us!
我耳中只有爵士乐的重低音
All I hear is a funky bass line.
我知道  因为他在放音乐
I know, because he's doing it!
快把音乐关掉
Stop turning the music on!
真有意思  去死吧你
Ha-ha! Very funny! Screw you!
怎么了  鲍勃
What's the matter, Bob,
你不喜欢劲爆舞曲吗
you don't like high energy dance music?!
杀人鲸  杀人鲸  杀人鲸  中了
Killer whale, killer whale, killer whale! Orca!
鲍鲍
Uh, Bobby?
Bobby?
孩子们  你们老爸呢
Have you kids seen your father?
你是说那个大胡子变态吗
You mean that creepy guy with the mustache?
-是的  -没看见
- Yeah. - No.
喂  我们正要睡觉呢
Hey, we're trying to sleep in here.
对不起
Sorry.
招财天使  感觉真好
Penny angel! Feels good.
撒在脸上感觉真好
Oh, feels good on my face!
钢蹦儿  钢蹦儿  钢蹦儿
Pennies, pennies, pennies.
老妈  我们说过了
Mom, we talked about this.
老妈  适可而止吧
Mom, stop.
你平常很乖的
You're better than this.
出来  出来  无论你在哪里
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
你犯了一个错误  弗拉缇
You made one mistake, Flarty.
你没有斩草除根
You let me live.
乘客们  明天我们将为您提供波塞冬早午餐
Passengers, join us tomorrow morning for Poseidon's Brunch,
还有主厨杜瓦尔的特色料理奥纳西斯牡蛎
featuring Chef Duval's famous Oysters Onassis.
琪琪很爱吃  你们也会爱吃的
Kiki loves them, and you will, too.
糟了  那些牡蛎
Oh, crap. The oysters.
划呀划呀划小船...
Row, row, row the boat...
杜瓦尔
Duval?
那里面是你吗
Is that you in there?
桶里面没有人  走开
No one's in this pot. Go away.
我是意大利面
I am the spaghetti.
杜瓦尔  你不是意大利面
Duval, you're not the spaghetti.
我就是
I am spaghetti.
放开盖子
Let go of the lid.
这里只有意大利面
Just spaghetti in here.
杜瓦尔  别闹了  我要离开这艘船
Duval, stop. I'm trying to get off the ship, all right?
不过你要先把那些牡蛎扔掉
But first you have to throw out those oysters.
如果我不用那些牡蛎做菜
If I don't serve the oysters,
弗拉缇就会逼我教老水手跳钢管舞
Flarty will make me teach pole-dancing to seniors.
可是如果你用它们  人们就会生病
But if you serve them, people can get really sick.
这就像是厨师的希波克拉底誓言  杜瓦尔
It's like the Hippocratic Oath of chefs, Duval,
医生从业誓言
不能有意害人生病
to not make people sick on purpose.
鲍勃
Bob...
干嘛
Yes?
吻我
Kiss me.
什么
What?
别压抑自己了
You know you want to.
不  我没有
No, I don't.
你刚才难道不想吻我吗
You didn't just want to kiss me just now?
不想
I didn't.
好吧  不过你说得很对
All right. But you're right.
来  我们马上把那些牡蛎扔掉  鲍勃
Come, let's throw out those horrible oysters right now, Bob!
这才对嘛
Now you're talking.
你先进  我随后
You first. Way in the back.
搞什么名堂
What the hell?!
杜瓦尔  给我开门
Duval, open the door!
你就在里面过夜吧
You spend the night in there.
虽然船长为人复杂
The captain is complicated,
不过他很清楚何为上策
but he knows what's best.
杜瓦尔  杜瓦尔
Duval! Duval!
我要吻你
I will kiss you.
太晚了  时不再来  鲍勃
Too late. The moment's gone, Bob.
杜瓦尔  我们可以再进一步
Duval! We can do more than kiss!
深入发展  杜瓦尔
Other things! Duval!
新鲜火腿
多亏你用的是罐装肉  杜瓦尔
Thanks for serving canned meat, Duval.
早上好  防风号上的各位
Good morning, Windbreakers!
期待大家尽情享用波塞冬早午餐
Looking forward to seeing you all at Poseidon's Brunch,
其中还有奥纳西斯牡蛎
featuring Oysters Onassis,
新鲜得就和当天捕到的一样
as well as the catch of the day.
刚才那句有点自卖自夸了啦
That one is a little shout-out for you-know-who.
他跑了
He's gone!
妈的  你去准备早午餐
Oh, damn it! You get the brunch ready!
你  你去找鲍勃
You! You find Bob!
他越是跑我越是想抓住他  是不是琪琪
When he runs, it only makes me want him more, right, Kiki?
琪琪  琪琪  琪琪
Kiki, Kiki, Kiki.
帮个忙
Little help!
真抱歉
Oh, sorry.
露易丝  过来  这里
Louise, come here. Over here.
是你啊  老爸
Oh, hey, dad.
弗拉缇彻底疯了
Flarty is absolutely insane.
他把我关在库房一整晚
He locked me in his walk-in overnight.
还要给乘客们吃烂牡蛎
He's gonna serve rotten oysters.
我们要阻止他
We've got to stop him.
老爸  你看
Oh, dad, watch this.
咔咔咔咔
Clackety-clackety-clackety-clackety,
咔咔咔咔咔  怎么样
click-click-click-click-clack. Huh?
露易丝  你到底帮不帮忙
Louise, are you gonna help me or not?
好  我帮
Okay, I'll help.
好  很好
All right, good.
首先  你去引开弗拉缇和他的手下
First, we need to distract Flarty and his crew
我去撤掉早午餐的牡蛎
while I take the oysters from the brunch.
我可是掩护专家
Well, I am a master of distraction.
知道了吧
See?
我要给你挣够100块  宝贝
I'm gonna get you that hundred bucks, baby.
不  这些是给玛丽莲的
No! Those are for Marilyn!
啊  不要  放手
Ah! No! Drop it!
每层甲板上都安排了寻找鲍勃的人手  长官
We have personnel on every deck looking for Bob, sir.
哈哈  我抓住你的耗子了
Ha-ha! I got your rat!
我的琪琪
My Kiki!
抓住她
Get her!
再见了  水手们
So long, seamen!
你要把这些牡蛎拿到哪去
Where are you taking the oysters?
相信我  你不会想吃的
Trust me, you don't want these.
还有许多别的东西可以吃的
There's plenty of other things to eat.
不用你告诉我什么能吃
Don't tell me what to eat!
放手  我这是在帮忙
Let go. I'm trying to help.
随意吃吧
Yeah, help yourself.
这东西肯定快吃没了
They must be running out!
我成功了  我引开他们了
I did it! I did the distraction!
通常情况下  露易丝
Typically, Louise,
掩护是把他们引开
when you do a distraction,
而不是把他们引来  好吗
you don't lead everybody to me, right?
好的
Right!
好了  下次吧
Okay, next time.
你怎敢利用琪琪
How dare you use Kiki
大搞阴谋破坏
in your sadistic game?
我搞阴谋破坏
My sadistic game?
没错  混蛋
That's right, buster.
你绑架了我们
You kidnapped us.
再次谢谢你
Thank you again.
我玩得很开心  船长
I'm having a wonderful time, Captain.
-琳达  你开什么玩笑  -怎么了
- Linda, are you kidding?! - What?
他没资格当船长
He shouldn't be captain.
谁当船长都比你称职
Anyone would be a better captain than you.
在我看来现在正在暴发一场叛乱
Sounds to me what's happening here is a mutiny!
叛乱
Ooh, mutiny?
这次航程的活动可真不少
This boat has so many activities!
来啊  鲍勃
Go ahead, Bob.
你想策动叛乱  请继续
You want a mutiny? Proceed.
-好啊  -来吧
- Okay. - Come on.
-你等着  -咱走着
- All right. - Let's go.
-我会的  -快点的
- I will. - Go ahead.
开始了
Here we go.
-各位...  -开始了
- Everybody... - Here we go.
-好了  让我...  -策动叛变啊
- All right, let me... - Call a mutiny.
-我正在  -非常好
- I'm doing it! - All right.
但如果你失败了  我就把你放在救生艇上
But if you fail, I'm putting you in a dinghy
只给你一个罗盘和一块饼干
with nothing but a compass and a biscuit.
好  很好  谁想跟我一起
Okay, fine. So who's with me?!
你怎么样
How about you,
望远镜短裤男
shorts-and-binoculars guy?
你恨死这里了
You hate it here.
或是你  看监狱的
Or you, prisoner guy.
我曾看见你被关在那个屋里  对吧
I saw you locked in that room, right?
你一定要支持我
You've got to be on my side.
别转过头去
Don't look away!
老爸  你要爆炸了
Oh, dad. Oh, you're bombing.
算了吧
Oh, forget it!
放到救生艇上
Get the dinghy!
我也想说这句
I wanna to say that.
船长  自助餐好像出问题了
Captain, there seems to be a problem with the buffet.
天啊
Oh, boy.
我就知道
Uh, yup.
我喜欢这支曲子
Ooh, I love this song.
玛丽莲  玛丽莲
Marilyn! Marilyn!
玛丽莲  你还好吗
Marilyn, are you okay?!
我找到了你的眼睛
I found your eye,
可是我没整到钱
but I couldn't get the money.
不过我会的
But I will.
小子  别提了  这只是一个骗局
Kid, forget it. It's just a scam!
什么
What?
老天
Oh, God.
听着  你是个好孩子
Listen, you're a sweet kid,
我这只老海牛根本
and you deserve better than an old--
配不上你
an old sea cow like me.
-可是  可是...  -别可是了
- But, but... - Save your buts.
有些事情注定不该发生
Some things just aren't meant to be.
眼睛你留着吧
Keep the eye.
他还有整整一箱呢
He's got a whole box of them somewhere.
这究竟是怎么回事
What the hell was that about?
我知道她是玩偶
I know she was a puppet,
但是她紧紧地抓住了我的心
but she put her hand right up my heart.
真恶心
Aw, sick!
别担心  吉恩
Don't worry, Gene,
海里还有很多海牛呢
there's plenty of manatees in the sea.
不过实际上没有多少了
But there's not, really,
因为它们正濒临灭绝
because they're endangered.
天啊
Mon dieu!
现在我们可以上岸了吧
Now can we go to some land?
这些人需要看医生
These people need a hospital.
放弃吧  鲍勃
Give it up, Bob.
你的叛乱失败了
Your mutiny failed.
杜瓦尔  在鲍勃的救生艇上弄个狗食袋
Duval, make Bob a doggie bag for his dinghy.
我不弄  船长
No, Captain.
什么  你是说不了吗
I'm sorry. Did you say no?
是的  我说了
Yes, I did.
我把我最美好的烹饪年华献给了你
I gave you the best cooking years of my life.
现在  我代表所有厨师和所有牡蛎
And now, on behalf of all cooks and all oysters,
命令你收回成命
I demand that you give up your command.
就是这样  杜瓦尔
There you go, Duval!
就是这样  鲍勃
There you go, Bob!
你被罢职了  厨师
You're relieved of your position, cook.
阿希  把鲍勃和杜瓦尔带出餐厅
Asch, remove Bob and Duval from the dining room.
阿希  阿希
Asch! Asch!
杜瓦尔说得对  我支持他
Duval is right, sir. I'm with him.
你的耗子屎我收拾够了
I've cleaned up enough of your messes!
陪船长回房间
Escort the captain to his stateroom.
好  你做得非常好
All right, you're doing great.
吻我
Kiss me!
不行  现在不行
Not now. Not a good time.
那什么时候
Then when?
快和那个法国人舌吻
French-kiss that Frenchman.
好吧  你赢了  鲍勃
Well, you've won, Bob.
不过你记住...
But remember this...
他说了什么
What'd he say?
没什么  只是打了个嗝
Nothing. He just burped.
我好想你  吉恩
I miss you, Gene.
我真的真的好想你
I really, really miss you.
有谁想要去痣吗
Anyone need a mole removed?
帮我挠挠背
Ah, peel my back.
看啊玛丽莲  生肉农场
Look, Marilyn, it's a meat farm.
好美啊
It's beautiful.
开什么玩笑
You've got to be kidding me.
我要去睡觉
I'm going to bed,
我现在不想收拾这个
I'm not dealing with this right now.
也许永远都不想收拾
Or maybe ever.
我从没这么放松过
Well, I've never felt more rested.
好似一幅蛋白质落日图
Like a protein sunset.
真美
It's nice.